This is a hot spot
숨 쉬듯 찾는 네 밥상
단골이 된 넌 fall in love
참을 수 없는 맛
우린 in the kitchen
Cookin' it up, what you craving?
나의 입맛대로 saucin'
And now the world's gone mad
You don't need to think too much
씹고 뜯고 맛보고 즐기다 가면 돼
(Yeah, yeah, yeah)
깊이 스며들어 in your mouth
(Ooh)
Guilty pleasure never killed nobody, 드셔봐
이빨 사이 낀 spaghetti
빼고 싶니? Bon appétit
그냥 포기해 어차피
Eat it up
Eat it up, eat it
Eat it up, eat it, eat it up
머릿속 낀 SSERAFIM
Bad dish in between your teeth
그냥 포기해 어차피
Eat it up
Eat it up, eat it
Eat it up, eat it, eat it up
Eat it up, eat it, eat it
Eat it up, eat it up
Eat it up
Eat it up, eat it
Eat it up, eat it, eat it up
Yeah, this is the sweet spot
Heat up the scene, it's that big shot
Chef's choice, 널 위한 킥이야
You lost in the sauce, no turnin' back
더 취할 거야 밤새, 기울여 절로
난 빈 잔은 받고, 이젠 핀잔은 걸러
좋은 게 좋은 거지 좋다는 게, 왜 뭐?
느껴봐 어서, 꺾지 말고, 벌컥
Snap it up like a Getty
내 김치 포즈는 여전히 priceless
Whatever I'm cookin', star같이
어떤 코스든 원하면 말아주는 쉐키
내가 네 취향 드라마 주인공이고
또 숨, 듣, 명이고, 고칼로리 Hеrshey 초코
모든 줏대를 홀리는 타로, 넌 음미해 나로
자 이제 까에서 빠로
자 이제 까에서 빠로, brr
Yeah, this is a hot spot
Don't give a fork, 네가 뭐라던
씹어보셔 맛이 좋아
필요 없어 three star
Yеah, 말로만 hate it
어디 갔어 너의 diet?
남몰래 쓱 하는 음미
You better stop lying
Don't care what you talk about
오늘도 제 발로 달려온 건 너잖아
(Yeah, yeah, yeah)
깊이 스며들어 in your mouth
(Ooh)
진짜 사랑인지 아닌지 곱씹어 봐
이빨 사이 낀 spaghetti
빼고 싶니? Bon appétit
그냥 포기해 어차피
Eat it up
Eat it up, eat it
Eat it up, eat it, eat it up
머릿속 낀 SSERAFIM
Bad dish in between your teeth
그냥 포기해 어차피
Eat it up
Eat it up, eat it
Eat it up, eat it, eat it up
Eat it up, eat it, eat it
Eat it up, eat it up
Eat it up
Eat it up, eat it
Eat it up, eat it, eat it up
Eat it up, eat it, eat it
Eat it up, eat it up
Eat it up
Eat it up, eat it
Eat it up, eat it, eat it up